http://www.progress.com/legal/privacy-center

ProductsNewDevOps & DevSecOpsChefAutomate your infrastructure to build, deploy, manage, and secure applications in modern cloud, hybrid, and on-premises environments.Cloud Native App Dev Platform KinveyNativeChatCognitive Services CorticonWeb Content Management SitefinityUI/UX Tools Kendo UITelerikTest StudioSecure Data Connectivity and Integration DataDirectSecure Managed File Transfer MOVEitOpenEdge OpenEdgeNetwork Monitoring WhatsUp GoldView All ProductsSolutionsDigital Experience Application Evolution Mobility Modern UI Health CloudServicesConsulting Education Modernization OutsourcingSupportSupport Support Center Customer Self Service Download Center Resources Documentation Knowledge Base How-To Videos Webinars Whitepapers Success Stories Community Enhancement Requests Blogs FAQsPartnersPartner Program Partner Specialties Partner Locator PartnerLink Former Ipswitch CommunityCompanyAbout Progress Company Overview Leadership Corporate Social Responsibility Careers Offices Customers News & Info Blogs Investor Relations Press Releases Press Coverage Recognitions Events Search LoginSupportLink PartnerLink Telerik Your Account1-800-477-6473 Ready to Talk?1-800-477-6473
GO
Privacy Center
Privacy at Progress
Progress Software Corporation, together with all of its subsidiaries and affiliates, including without limitation Telerik EAD and Kinvey, Inc. (“Progress Software”, “we”, “us”, “our” or the “Company”) is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company’s web sites, individuals who register to use our services, and individuals who register to attend the Company’s corporate events.
You can learn more about Progress’ commitment to privacy and data security by reading the following:
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Privacy Shield Statement
HIPAA FAQs
Privacy Highlights
Important information
Progress’ full Privacy Policy contains more information about the Company’s privacy practices.
Progress has certified certain of its services under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. For more information on our Privacy Shield compliance, please click here.
Progress is HIPAA compliant and operates highly secure computing environments in its corporate offices, development environments, and production cloud products. Progress audits its security solutions and processes annually to maintain SOC2 and HIPAA validation.
For more information about Progress’ HIPAA practices, click here.
Progress is Committed to Protecting Your Personal Information
Personal Information Collection
Progress may collect, process, and retain information about you when you visit our websites or use our products or services.
If you choose to participate in the Progress Community, you may choose to provide us with additional information such as a photo, social media profiles, areas of expertise, and other information. We may combine other publicly available information related to the organization from which you work for with the information that you provide to us.
Progress and our service providers may observe your activities, interactions, preferences, transactional information, and other computer and connection information (such as IP address) relating to your use of our websites and our products or services. This may be on a personal (with your consent) or non-personal basis.
We may also use log files, cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages you view, links you click on, and other actions you may take when accessing our websites, products, services, or emails.
How information about you will be used
Progress Software may use the information we collect about you to:
Provide you with the websites and any support you may request;
Respond to your inquiries or fulfill your requests;
Diagnose website technical problems;
Send you information that we believe may be of interest to you, such as product announcements, newsletters, educational materials, and upcoming events;
Send you administrative information such as notices related to product, service, or policy changes;
Understand how our websites, products, and services are being used;
Personalize your experience on our websites and present products or features that are tailored to your interests; and
Prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activity.
Sharing your data
Unless described in the full Privacy Policy, Progress does not share, sell, rent, or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes.
Data Processing
Personal information collected by Progress may be stored and processed in the United States or in any other country where Progress or its affiliates, subsidiaries or third-party service providers maintain facilities. When you opt-in and provide personal information to Progress, you consent to the processing and transfer of your information within the United States and around the world.
Communication Preferences
All Marketing emails from Progress will contain a link to the Progress Preference Center where you can control which email communications you receive from us.
For additional information about requests to access, change or delete your information, please click here.
Information Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please refer to the Contact Us section below.
We will respond to your request within a reasonable time.
We may need to retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Contact us
If you have comments or questions about this Policy, you may contact us by mail e-mail (Privacy@progress.com) or by regular mail at:
PSC Data Protection Officer
14 Oak Park Drive
Bedford MA 01730
USA
Learn more
Privacy Center
Privacy Policy
California Resident Privacy Notice
Privacy
Questions about Progress’ privacy practices and how we handle your personal data
privacy@progress.com
Copyrights
Use of Progress Software copyrighted materials or notice of copyright infringement
copyrights@progress.com
Trademarks
Questions about or requests to use Progress Software trademarks, logos or branding
trademarks@progress.com
General legal
legal@progress.com
Governance
bod@progress.com
Security
Questions about Security, Privacy, Compliance and Due Diligence
security@progress.com
Copyright © 2020 Progress Software Corporation and/or its subsidiaries or affiliates.All Rights Reserved.
Progress, Telerik, Ipswitch, and certain product names used herein are trademarks or registered trademarks of Progress Software Corporation and/or one of its subsidiaries or affiliates in the U.S. and/or other countries. See Trademarks for appropriate markings.
Terms of Use
Privacy Center
Security Center
Trademarks
License Agreements
Careers
Offices
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
